And the result.
I'm here to deliver the delivery!
Sorry for the wait!
I'm sorry, I drank the order.
I was thirsty and drank the order.
Would you like orange juice and taco
rice?
Here you are.
Please enjoy your meal!
Hello!
I came to do my own business.
Hello.
Today, I'm wearing this horn.
Can you see it?
It's a horn.
Everyone...
Oh, I can see the TV.
There's something on it!
I'll take it off!
It's a cookie!
Muji brought it!
It looks delicious! What kind of cookie
is it?
It's a chocolate cookie.
This is delicious.
Do you know what this is?
Is this white chocolate?
It looks delicious!
The focus is on the chocolate cookie.
What do you think?
Trick or Treat!
I can't give it to you!
If you don't give me a snack, I'll play
a prank on you.
I have to play a prank on you!
Here you are.
Thank you!
I got all of them.
There's 28 minutes left.
30 minutes!
There's 28 minutes left, and the first
part will start.
It's starting!
There are always two truths.
The team is disbanded.
The truth is always two.
We are the main detective, Juri & Aki.
We will solve your problems today.
Bye bye!
I'll eat it now.
Let's eat.
Yes.
Wow.
Look, isn't it great?
I'm the only one who's focused.
Wait a minute.
It's a good song.
We're about 15 minutes before the
actual performance.
What should we do?
I have to focus.
Juri, you should focus more.
I'm nervous.
What about this hand?
Left.
I'm glad.
What should I do?
I'm nervous.
What?
It's hot.
I'm nervous.
Why are you like this?
Yes, yes.
I think everyone would be surprised if
we were in the venue.
It's like a Halloween live.
Yes, it's like a surprise Halloween
live.
Some people are a little bit aware of
it.
I saw it on the video.
I was surprised when I saw the
audience.
What?
What is the curtain?
No, no, no.
It's already open.
Plan 25.
The coupon key!
It's the first time I've heard of it.
The coupon key in Canada is the cute
coupon key!
It's good, isn't it?
I like it.
But Juri, you know, the throbbing...
The throbbing...
Juri, you said the throbbing...
I thought the throbbing was a sword at
first.
But it's a foot, so...
It's a kick.
I thought it was a kick.
The throbbing...
The foot at that time is really
beautiful.
I'll give you a kick.
OK!
Please subscribe to our channel!
What's that?
It's a mirror.
It's soft.
What's that?
I don't know.
It's like a giraffe.
It's so cool.
It's so beautiful.
We'll do our best!
We'll do a prank.
We'll do something.
I couldn't hear you.
Hello everyone!
Thank you!
Thank you for coming to the Super
Tokimeki Shonen Bun broadcasted by
Ikuze!
I'm Aki-chan, aka Super Tokimeki Lemon,
and I'm Aki Suda.
I'm Okanami, aka Super Tokimeki Blue,
and I'm Okanami Otsuja.
I'm Hitoka, aka Super Tokimeki Red, and
I'm Hitoka Sakai.
Thank you!
Tanomi, Julia, Hitoko, Haruka, Aki,
Hiyori, Super Dope Advertisement,
Rock'n'Roll!
Thank you for watching!
The Cross
We, CLOSER
3, 2, 1, 0
I'm going!
Thank you for watching!
1 minute is over!
20 seconds have passed.
Tenten camera!
Yaho!
It's like a dream.
Everyone's song is so cute.
From the back.
I like this one.
It's like a wedding ceremony.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Here it is!
This is our favorite!
We're going to start part 2!
Yay!
Let's do our best!
This is part 2, but...
Part 2
We will definitely make the future
brighter with everyone, so let's keep
running up any wall together!
I don't want to lose, I'll live up to
my name!
I'll be the strongest!
I'll say hello to my new self!
I don't care what they say, I'll be the
strongest!
Because I've fallen in love with you!
My feelings for you will soon turn into
love!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Outside the War
To be continued
The legend was to save, spring, the
couple for the future,
But runaway against the long cold
blizzard
Begin real
Frustration
Or vanish
Immortals
Second have you had a hard time the
most?
Thank you.
Bye bye!
it's like those streaming stations
what the heck is this
that's how full of energy they are
Tokyo concert is over
theó
well, just kidding
let's enjoy it
Let's enjoy it
I'll always draw you
My precious feelings
Sometimes, I'll be by your side
And I'll be flippant
Because I'm always thinking about you
Thank you for watching!
I'm always lonely
You are the source of my energy
Please stay by my side from now on
My heart is pounding, it's because of
you
Finally, finally, we meet again
I'm always lonely
I'm happy in the world
Only you
Sometimes it's your fault
Because tomorrow will be more cute
Always, always, next to you
I hope I can be
A little more cute
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching!